Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Executive Records
  - Subseries C. SDF Full-time Operations 1981-1988
    - Subsubseries 2. SDF Board of Trustees
      - A. Articles & By-Laws
        - Bylaws and ammendments, c. 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - B. Minutes
        - Board of Trustees Minutes.1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Board of Trustees Minutes. 1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Board of Trustees Minutes. 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Board of Trustees Minutes. 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Board of Trustees Minutes. 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - Minutes and notes, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Minutes and notes, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - C. Agenda Materials
        - Meeting materials, c. Dec. 1980-Feb. 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - Meeting materials, Apr. 27, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - Memo to Trustees, May 12, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
        - Workshop materials and notes,June 1-2, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - Meeting materials #1June 22, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - Meeting materials #2June 22, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - Meeting materials #3June 22, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials and notes #1Aug. 13-14, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - Agenda materials and notes #2Aug. 13-14, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - Agenda materials and notes #3Aug. 13-14, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - Agenda materials and notes #4Aug. 13-14, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, Aug. 13-14, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials, Oct. 20-21, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials and administrative notes, Oct. 20-21, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, Dec. 14, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, Dec. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Board materials and notes, June-Dec. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Board materials, c. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, #1Feb. 1-2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Agenda materials, #2Feb. 1-2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2 #1Feb. 1-2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2 #2Feb. 1-2, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials,Feb. 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #1Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #2Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #3Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #4Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, copy 3Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - Meeting planning materials, Apr. 5-6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, Apr. 1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #1June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #2June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #3June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #4June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #5June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #6June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, "First installment," copy 1 #1June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
        - Agenda materials, "First installment," copy 1 #2June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - Agenda materials, "First installment," copy 2 #1June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials, "First installment," copy 2 #2June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials, "First installment," copy 3June 13-15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
        - Proposal materials for Board #1June 1982 (Box 22, Folder 13)
        - Proposal materials for Board #2June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Proposal materials for Board #3June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Proposal materials for Board #4June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Proposal materials for Board #5June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Proposal materials for Board #6June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Proposal materials for Board, Reviewer's cv'sJun. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - [R] Additional proposal materials #1Jun. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - [R] Additional proposal materials #2Jun. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - "What Where We've Been Says About Where We Are: Research and Information Science". Martha West, Prepared for June 1982 Board meetingMay 1982. (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials #1c. June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials #2c. June 1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #1Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Agenda materials, #2Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials, #3Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials, #4Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, #5Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, #6Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2 #1Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Agenda materials, #2Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, #3Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Agenda materials, copy 3 #1Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Agenda materials, #2Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials, #3Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials, #4Sep. 12-14, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, Sep. 1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #1Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
        - Agenda materials, #2Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials, #3Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials, #4Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, #5Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, #6Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Agenda materials, Materials from binder pocketDec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2 #1Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #2Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #3Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #4Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #5Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials, Accompanying materialsDec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Seminar on Natural and Computer Languages handouts,Dec. 6, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, Dec. 5-7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - Miscellaneous Board materials, c. 1982 (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1Mar. 13-15, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2Mar. 13-15, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, c. Mar. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials, copy 1 #1June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Agenda materials, #2June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Agenda materials, #3June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, #4June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Agenda materials, copy 2 #1June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - Agenda materials, #2June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, #3June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Agenda materials, #4June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Agenda materials, #5June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials, copy 3June 12-14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials,June-July 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - Agenda materials, special meeting, copy 1July 14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Agenda materials, special meeting, copy 2July 14, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Agenda materials, special meeting, copy 1Sep 12-13, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Agenda materials, special meeting, copy 2Sep 12-13, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, c. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Board resolutions, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - Agenda materials, Dec. 11-13, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Secretary's materials, Dec. 11-13, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Preparatory materials, Dec. 11-13, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous meeting materials, c. 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials, Feb 12-13, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Feb 12-13, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol IMay 13-15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials, Vol. IIMay 13-15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. I, copy 2May 13-15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. II, copy 2May 13-15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. IAug. 12-14, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Agenda materials, Vol. IIAug. 12-14, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. I, copy 2Aug. 12-14, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. II, copy 2Aug. 12-14, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Dec. 2-3, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Dec. 2-3, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. I Feb. 10-11, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Agenda materials, Vol. II Feb. 10-11, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. I, copy 2 Feb. 10-11, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. II, copy 2 Feb. 10-11, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 20)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. IMay 19-20, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 21)
        - Agenda materials, Vol. II [NOTE: There is no copy 2 volume I]May 19-20, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 22)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. II, copy 2May 19-20, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 23)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. IAug. 11-12, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 24)
        - Agenda materials, Vol. IIAug. 11-12, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. I, copy 2Aug. 11-12, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Vol. II, copy 2Aug. 11-12, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - [R] Agenda materials #1Nov. 10-11, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials #2Nov. 10-11, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Nov. 10-11, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
        - [R] Agenda materials #1Feb. 9-10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials #2Feb. 9-10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Feb. 9-10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - [R] Agenda materials, May 18-19, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Agenda materials supplementMay 18-19, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2May 18-19, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - [R] Agenda materials, supplementMay 18-19, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #1Aug. 10-11, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
        - Agenda materials, #2Aug. 10-11, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Aug. 10-11, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Nov. 9-10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 17)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Nov. 9-10, 1986copy 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Feb. 8-9, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Tab O Feb. 8-9, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2 Feb. 8-9, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Tab O, copy 2 Feb. 8-9, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
        - [R] Agenda materials #1May 17-18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Agenda materials #2May 17-18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2May 17-18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - [R] [R] Agenda materials #1 July 26-27, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Agenda materials #2 July 26-27, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2 July 26-27, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - [R] Agenda materials #1Nov. 8-9, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Agenda materials #2Nov. 8-9, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - [R]Agenda materials, copy 2 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - [R] Agenda materials, Mar. 6-7, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2Mar. 6-7. 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - [R] Agenda materials, #1June 12-13, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Agenda materials #2June 12-13, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Agenda materials #3June 12-13, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - Agenda materials, supplementJune 12-13, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2June 12-13, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - [R] Agenda materials, copy 2, supplementJune 12-13, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Meeting arrangements, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Meeting arrangements, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Meeting arrangements, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Meeting arrangements, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - D. Reports to Board
        - "What Where We've Been Says About Where We Are: Research and Information Science," Martha West, May 1982 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - "What Where We've Been Says About Where We Are: Research and Information Science," Martha West, copy 2May 1982 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - "A Systems Methodology for Basic Research in Language Use," Bill Woods [NOTE: Missing after Oct. 1989 earthquake and subsequent moves.] (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - "An Overview of Programming Language Research," Toni Cohen [NOTE: Missing after Oct. 1989 earthquake and subsequent moves.] (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Selected excerpts from the annual reports of research projects funded by The System Development Foundation, copy 11985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - Selected excerpts from the annual reports of research projects funded by The System Development Foundation, copy 21985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - Selected excerpts from the annual reports of research projects funded by The System Development Foundation, copy 11986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - Selected excerpts from the annual reports of research projects funded by The System Development Foundation, copy 21986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Proceedings of the symposium on "Research Opportunities in Hearing." [NOTE: See also Series IV.B.2, Benchmark Symposia files]1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - E. Investment Committee
        - TAPE[R] Investment Committee. Tape of meeting (Box 1)
        - TAPE[R] Investment Committee. Tape of meeting (Box 1)
        - Investment Committee minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Investment Committee minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Investment Committee minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Investment Committee minutes. Agenda materialsSep. 1981 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Investment Committee materials #1c. 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Investment Committee materials #2c. 1981 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Investment Committee. Agenda materials, copy 1Dec. 11, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Investment Committee. Agenda materials, copy 2Dec. 11, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - F. Legal Matters
        - Memorandum of contentions of fact and law, Attorneys for Plaintiffs, copy 1Nov. 1982 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Memorandum of contentions of fact and law, Attorneys for Plaintiffs, copy 2Nov. 1982 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Memorandum of contentions of fact and law, Attorneys for Defendants, copy 1 Nov. 1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Memorandum of contentions of fact and law, Attorneys for Defendants, copy 2Nov. 1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - Documents distributed to Trustees for July 14, 1983 meetingca. 1983 July (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Summons.Aug. 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - President's file #11980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - President's file #21980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - President's file #31980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Settlement letters, 1985, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Qualifying distributions, Dec. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Cooley, Godward, et al. Attorneys file #1c. 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Cooley, Godward, et al. Attorneys file #2c. 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - G. Meeting tapes, 1981 - 1988
        - [R] Tapes of meetings held June 1981 - June 1988 (Box 1)
        - [R] Tapes of meetings held June 1981 - June 1988 (Box 2)
        - [R] Tapes of meetings held June 1981 - June 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - H. Oral Histories of Trustees
        - Beckman, Arnold O. Transcript (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Morrisett, Lloyd N. Transcript and tapes (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Putt, Donald. Transcript and tapes (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Tyler, Ralph W. Transcript and tapes [NOTE: Cassettes are stored in Cassette Box 3 shelved at the end of Series I] (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Subsubseries 3. President. Office files
      - A. President's Papers
        - President's papers, Oct. 1980, Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - President's papers, Mar. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 13)
        - President's papers, Apr. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - President's papers, May 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - President's papers, June 1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - President's papers, July 1981 (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - President's papers, Aug. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - President's papers, Sep.-Oct. 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - President's papers, Dec. 1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - President's papers, Jan.-Feb. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - President's papers, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - President's papers, May-June 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - President's papers, July-Aug. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - President's papers, Sep.-Oct. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - President's papers, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - President's papers, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - President's papers, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - President's papers, May-June 1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
        - President's papers, July 1983 (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - President's papers, Aug.-Dec. 1983 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - President's papers, Jan.-June 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - President's papers, July-Dec. 1984 (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - President's papers, Jan.-Aug. 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - President's papers, Sep.-Dec. 1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - President's papers, Feb.-Aug. 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - President's papers, Feb.-Dec. 1987 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - President's papers, Jan.-Mar. 1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - President's papers, Apr.-June 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - President's papers, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - B. Setting Up Program
        - Developing program #1c.1981 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - Developing program #2c.1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Developing program #3c.1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Direction of foundation, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - [R] Employee policy file, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Subsubseries 4. Director of Programs. Office files
      - A. Working files
        - Director of Programs. Budget working file, c. 1981-c. 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Director of Programs. Memos, notes and correspondence, c. 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Director of Programs. Foundation executive salaries #1c. 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Director of Programs. Foundation executive salaries #2c. 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Director of Programs. Information science memorandum. Drafts and comments, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Director of Programs. History of science file, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - B. Correspondence and memoranda
        - Director of Programs. Memoranda file, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Director of Programs. Memoranda file, 1982-1983 and undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Director of Programs. Correspondence, May-June 1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Director of Programs. Memoranda to Trustees, Aug. 1981-Nov. 1983 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - C. Programmatic Subject file
        - Allen, Dr. William R. Princeton University (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - American Electronics Association. Pat H. Hubbard (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Branscomb, Dr. Lewis. IBM (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Butler, Brett. Information Access Corporation. Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - Butler, Brett. Publications #1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Butler, Brett. Publications #2 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Butler, Brett. Strategic Plans (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Butler, Brett. Corporate Business Plan1979-1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - Butler, Brett. Corporate Business Plan 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - California Library Authority for Systems and Services (CLASS) (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Cohen, A. Toni. Correspondence and drafts. Dec. 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Cohen, A. Toni. Nov. 1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Cohen, A. Toni. July-Oct. 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Cohen, A. Toni. Undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Command, Control, Communications and Intelligence (C3I), 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Computer arts (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Dolby/Clark--Petroleum Statement, Monthly. Meeting notes and correspondence #11981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Dolby/Clark--Petroleum Statement, Monthly. Meeting notes and correspondence #21981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Dolby/Clark--Petroleum Statement, Monthly. Meeting notes and correspondence #31981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Dolby/Clark--Petroleum Statement, Monthly. Meeting notes and correspondence #4 1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - EDUCOM. Carolyn P. Landis (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - EDUCOM. Information sheets and publications #1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - EDUCOM. Information sheets and publications #2 (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - Freedman, David. Papers and comments, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - Fujimura, Osamu. Papers and comments, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #2 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #5 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #7 (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #8 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Correspondence and papers #9 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Pragmatica Systems, Inc.--Susan Leigh Star (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #2 (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #4 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #5 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #6 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Gerson, Elihu. Population realignment book file #7 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Godfrey, Michael D. #1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Godfrey, Michael D. #2 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Holmes, Heather. Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Knuth, Donald. NSF proposal file #1 (Box 40, Folder 9)